digitaldesire.com 2009-12-18

# Digital Desire - Official Tour - Terms and Conditions

Privacy Policy 

## Privacy Policy

We do not, and will not, distribute, rent or sell any personally identifiable information to third parties without your express consent, other than as necessary to process your credit card payment; unless requested via a subpoena, court order, or local, state, federal or international law enforcement request. 

We use your information solely in order to process your credit card payment, to facilitate your viewing of our web site and to communicate with you. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and web site usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to identify you personally. Digital Desire uses your email address to send periodic email newsletters and promotional email to you about services and products offered. You can indicate at any time that you do not wish to receive e-mail information from us. We do not provide your e-mail to third parties without your express consent. 

Digital Desire takes reasonable precautions to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about you. We provide you with a secure web page for you to submit your billing information.We maintain your personally identifiable information in a reasonably secure manner including storing such information behind firewalls. Digital Desire recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this web site or your dealings with Digital Desire, please contact us at [legal@digitaldesire.com](mailto:legal@digitaldesire.com) or by mail at: Digital Desire c/o DHD Media, 520 Washington Blvd, #445, Marina Del Rey, California 90292.

Digital Desire is not responsible for the content or the privacy polices of web sites to which it may provide links or the websites of its advertisers. 

* * *

* * *

All models were 18 years of age or older at the time of photography.   
Your use of this site is protected. Read our [Privacy Policy](http://www.digitaldesire.com/terms.html)
